A Guide to the John A. Hartford Foundation records, Grants, Series 1 FA771
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1984-2010; 1
  - University of Kansas: D. Swagerty (2000-0447), 2000-2003 (Box 110, Folder 765-767)
  - University of Medicine and Dentistry of New Jersey: R. K. Steel (96-0187), 1996-2003 (Box 110, Folder 768-770)
  - University of Medicine and Dentistry of New Jersey: R. K. Steel (96-0187), 1996-2003 (Box 111, Folder 771-777)
  - University of Medicine and Dentistry of New Jersey: R. K. Steel (96-0187), 1996-2003 (Box 112, Folder 778-784)
    - University of Medicine and Dentistry of New Jersey: R. K. Steel (96-0187), 1996-2003; 2014:023:011; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 9972)
  - University of Medicine and Dentistry of New Jersey: R. K. Steel (96-0187), 1996-2003 (Box 113, Folder 785-787)
  - University of Michigan: J. Halter (99-0344), 1999-2004 (Box 113, Folder 788-790)
  - University of Michigan: R. Dunkle (99-0689), 1999-2004 (Box 113, Folder 791)
  - University of Michigan: R. Dunkle (99-0689), 1999-2004 (Box 114, Folder 792-798)
  - University of Michigan: R. Dunkle (99-0689), 1999-2004 (Box 115, Folder 799-800)
  - University of North Carolina: J. Busby-Whitehead (96-0346), 1996-2000 (Box 115, Folder 801-804)
  - University of North Carolina: J. Busby-Whitehead (96-0346), 1996-2000 (Box 116, Folder 805-806)
    - University of North Carolina: J. Busby-Whitehead (96-0346), 1996-2000; 2014:023:012; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11152)
  - University of Pennsylvania: N. Strumpf (95-0216), 1995-1997 (Box 116, Folder 807-809)
  - University of Pennsylvania: R. Lavizzo-Mourey/J. Johnson (99-0538), 1999-2004 (Box 116, Folder 810-811)
  - University of Pennsylvania: R. Lavizzo-Mourey/J. Johnson (99-0538), 1999-2004 (Box 117, Folder 812-813)
  - University of Pittsburgh: N. Resnick (2000-0485), 2000-2005 (Box 117, Folder 814-816)
  - University of Rochester: W. Hall (94-0160), 1994-1997 (Box 117, Folder 817-818)
  - University of Rochester: W. Hall (94-0160), 1994-1997 (Box 118, Folder 819-822)
  - University of Rochester: J. Bennett (97-0357), 1997-2003 (Box 118, Folder 823-825)
  - University of Rochester: J. Bennett (97-0357), 1997-2003 (Box 119, Folder 826-830)
  - University of Rochester: J. Bennett (99-0539), 1999-2001 (Box 119, Folder 831-832)
  - University of Rochester: J. Bennett (99-0539), 1999-2001 (Box 120, Folder 833-834)
  - University of Rochester: W. Hall (2000-0454), 2000-2005 (Box 120, Folder 835-836)
  - University of Texas Health Science Center, San Antonio: D. Espino (97-0300), 1997-2001 (Box 120, Folder 837-838)
  - University of Texas Health Science Center, San Antonio: D. Espino (97-0300), 1997-2001 (Box 121, Folder 839)
  - University of Texas Health Science Center, San Antonio: J. Williams/P. Noel (98-0296), 1998-2005 (Box 121, Folder 840-843)
  - University of Texas Health Science Center, San Antonio: D. Espino, MD (2000-0436), 2000-2005 (Box 121, Folder 844-845)
  - University of Washington: W. Katon (98-0301), 1998-2005 (Box 122, Folder 846-850)
  - University of Washington: I. Abrass (99-0345), 1999-2006 (Box 122, Folder 851)
  - University of Washington: I. Abrass (99-0345), 1999-2006 (Box 123, Folder 852-853)
  - University of Wisconsin: N. Shahidi (76-0293), 1976-1985 (Box 123, Folder 854-856)
  - University of Wisconsin: M. Sager (99-0240), 1999-2004 (Box 123, Folder 857-858)
  - University of Wisconsin: M. Sager (99-0240), 1999-2004 (Box 124, Folder 859-861)
  - Vanderbilt University Medical Center: W. Ray (94-0251), 1994-2002 (Box 124, Folder 862-865)
  - Vanderbilt University Medical Center: W. Ray (94-0251), 1994-2002 (Box 125, Folder 866-868)